He didn’t ask for it. He wasn’t expecting it. He’s not prepared for it.
Tooth Fairy 2 is a comedy, family film directed by Alex Zamm.
Larry Guthrie, who loses his first love to the town hot shot, decides to win her
back by volunteering with the children at her after-school program.
When Larry accidentally tells the kids the Tooth Fairy is make-believe, he soon is
transformed into a tutu-clad fairy with the "sentence" of collecting teeth.
Larry Guthrie, played by Larry the Cable Guy.
Nyx, played by Brady Reiter.
Brooke, played by Erin Beute.
Customer, played by John Connon.
Gabe McKee, played by Gabriel Suttle.
Sydney Wilder, played by Sydney Rouviere.
Tooth Fairy 2 is a 2012 American fantasy comedy family film directed by
Alex Zamm and starring Larry the Cable Guy in the lead role.
It is the stand-alone sequel to the 2010 film
Tooth Fairy, starring Dwayne Johnson.
It was released direct-to-video on DVD and Blu-ray on March 6, 2012.
The tone is lighthearted.